what I had first was these this length
here in these size plates and I had them
every
second one of these
circles and that made up the full length
of
that and then I brought them in to every
thirst which was giving you a certain
Gap a smaller gap which means the unit
then was that big and it was placed into
this we got it mhm first one as you can
see was that
white the next one was 2 3 4 5 6 seven
there that wi which is the same width as
a cap
mhm bit smaller than the cap so could
almost one that just sit in the tube
down that those seven
plates in this are we in those seven
plates in this in line positive both
ends negative
Center produce gas off both sides of
every plate tremendously except the
outside plat except the that way and
that way yes all the way through
negative Center and your current flow
both ways of both sides of your neutral
plates the only plates connected are 1
Center one positive both n ones as seven
plates so you had two neutral and two
neutral each side so you had positive
neutral neutral negative neutral neutral
positive and that then run a l
p76
4.4 4400 v8 car
right can we see that happening without
the just certain in the water how the
all the plates are producing without
being connected running a
car no no
petrol why went to L
back what it didn't do Mr r y what it
didn't do is because we had was
Poli because we
had a PO them
case this here you can't Bo by
hand but when you put vacuum these units
here inside that this container the lid
on your positive negative connected
through this tube here was your spout
for taking the gas
off your plates
we're down in the middle mhm this then
screwed on and an end cap the same this
one here had a the gas shed water to the
level you getting it Y water to the
level this in here was air space gas
space spout out here with your hose on
it to your int how did you connect the
wi through the C yes I put a out each
end through mhm put a bolt through each
end so I could hook me wires on in the
middle from positive to positive I just
Loop the wire over the top just to join
the two end plates because only had it
connected to one end so then both ends
and the middle one had a bolt right
through the center insulated just to the
center plate all right so we had a
negative and a positive out here in a
wire over um the gas come off here now
on idle stainless one was it
no it's doesn't matter it wasn't in the
water it just loed over over the top
yeah oh this she Lo while the plates are
in here I just clipped it put a little
alligator clip on there took it over the
top and alligator click on here you see
so B it was not in the water no not in
the water didn't matter anyway now with
this lid
on screwed down and your tube out here
on the idle of the
vehicle the L this unit did not Flex in
or
out when you gave the vehicle a
REV this
lid expanded up probably an inch to an
inch and a half expansion
outwards which was very
dangerous the
motor instead doing what it should have
done this is all going instead of doing
what it should have done um polluted
very badly pollution fume smoke
everything else out the oil filler cap
the dip stick and the pollution valve in
the taper cover the motor run but was
not as powerful as um as
petrol at that stage with
a polye
unit the oppos it happens when you
use solid
stainless when you use a solid stainless
um uh
cylinder your cylinder does not extend
or
contract what then happens to your
motor is instead of pressurizing fume
out from your positions around your
pollution positions it then has a vacuum
you with the vehicle going if you pull
the dipstick out the motor will stall if
you loosen off the filler cap oil filler
cap the motor will St that's with this
solid un with a solid unit
[Music]
yes poine has pressure out solid unit
has a vacuum pull
inwards you can put your finger over a
little the little tiny hole in the
Tapper cover where you just a small h
comes off and the motor runs smooth take
your finger off she'll start shaking
like anything can stall out she has a
suction on your finger M with a polye
one has a pressure with a stainless one
you can increase your performance three
times over M Power vacuum in your
manifold when you back
off um
speed and you have brake
horsepower by just backing on your
accelerator your motor will feel like
your your car will feel like you're
using the brakes where it's not it sort
of works the opposite way with a solid
unit works the opposite way to what
exhaust brakes do on a truck exhaust
brakes shut off the the flow of gas
outwards so you store your motor and it
uses the brakes to slow your vehicle
down and gear this seems to work on the
intake a solid unit works on the intake
and has a similar thing when you back
off on the accelerator you feel like
your nose do mhm with a polye one or a
one which can expand it can be thin
stainless like we showed you on that
other one it can be thin stainless which
under vacuum will expand instead of
Contracting in like it should it expands
out and when it expands
out you your motor uses the gas what the
vacuum pulls off but the units gas which
I I'm only surmising this the units gas
what he can put off under atmospheric
pressure doesn't get used by the motor
it's the thing what expands as far as I
can figure out and then when you back
off on the accelerator and then go for
the
braks you should have manifold vacuum
but what happens is that pressure in the
cylinders by the bo outwards then
transfers into the manifold and you SE
the race ahead and you go for the brakes
there is no cuz you have no manifold
vacuum it's just transfer that pressure
into the manifold where a solid unit
does the complete
opposite you've got instant power on
you've got instant back off M and you
also have the um the manifold which
locks
up holding you back with the brakes on a
solid
unit and you also have extra brake hor
by your actual foot break M because you
you have instantly have that that you
have that yeah so solid containers are
the way to go mhm with a poine unit or a
flexible unit if you're trying to get
your pollution down like your exhaust
pollution and your motor
pollution that is not the way to go with
a flexible unit because it has pressure
solid unit is the way to go because then
she does not have any uh exhaust
emission mhm it doesn't have any
manifold motor Tapper cover dipstick oil
filler cap any pressure in your motor at
all in fact it has a vacuum to your
motor no oil usage that's the way to
go just that
one but if we can okay well I could have
the
temperature your motor should run
somewhere around about 90 this is a
solid unit right on the r on the solid
unit run around about 90 on the
temperature gauge when you hooked up the
solid unit to it she went to instant
cold the motor just run dead cold and it
wanted to perform better on dead cold
you couldn't get it hot and you take it
off and put it back on the Petr she
would come straight back up to your to
your um medium or normal
running even she would even override
your thermostat everything so that means
that there is a reaction in the m
we can pour
that see which plates produce at the
same
time if you wanted to I think I've got a
grinder in there you could cut some of
these off those ones yeah to all the be
equal can you get that down in there
it's down all right try
again
just and now you're not connected
[Music]
getting it
there
yep see if you had the same length tubes
and you put them in the water you would
fill that bucket completely you just run
out over the top and equally show you
each side of each plate why don't we
just put it in that then cuz that that
okay this tu's got a a
solid that water is pretty
slippery yeah you probably pulling the
apart now okay we can put that into the
bucket we can put the M on the
outside and we can put a negative down
the
Cent right and both sides of
this will produce in the water out here
and in the water in there right there no
connection no connection through the
water that'd be a good one to show
connection between to the stainless the
stainless no at the center one which is
is then connected to nothing
neutral we then have the outside
one which is this
size MH blocked off at the bottom full
of
water bucket got water in it not
connected to
it the neutral plate in the center will
produce gas off both sides not being
connected to positive negative can we
put Mes in the backet and try we will
when we do this next time love be
right
okay
producing did um did we see what
happened oh guess it's just
[Music]
coming did we catch that yep so done
right what I want to do is clear that
and if you could get down
that negative neutral
plate I need to lift it up
Jo that negative neutral part right I'm
going have to lift up the whole
thing take it
out what I'll do is I like I'll just
touch on and off so you can see where
she produces mhm
[Music]
gas isn't
it you see
[Music]
M very low
current about with one neutral plate
about bit less than half the ampage use
as uh negative Center and positive
outside when you put one neutral plate
not touching anything your
current um ampage use is about
half M if you make it put another plate
in two plates it goes down half of that
again and produces twice the gas